in the form of people,
виде людей
I am from Ukraine, the city of Khmelnitsky, the
я из Украины город Хмельницкого
Altai Republic, the Altai Territory,
республика алтайли Алтайский край
because there I am not so why they
потому что там я так не по из-за чего
divided a separate Republic into a separate
разделили отдельную Республику отдельно
region, like this, our great Mighty
край вот так наши великие Могучие
communist leaders once
коммунистические лидеры в свое время
divided because there are
поделили потому что там алтайцев там
less than 100 thousand Altaians there,
меньше 100 тысяч
in fact
на самом деле
it is  A mountainous republic Or maybe
она Горная республика А может
geographical features
географических особенностей
Yes, let’s say it was ethnically
Да да это скажем так этнически
national it was exactly like that
национально было именно так
Yes, I’m interested in talking specifically
Да мне интересно пообщаться именно
asking princes I’m interested in
спрашиваю принцев Мне интересно как
how ordinary people are doing, in fact, how
поживает обычные люди на самом деле как
do you think how ordinary people are doing during
вы думаете как поживает обычные люди во
a war When your country is attacked,
время войны Когда ваша страна нападает
it goes to certain  territories of
она идет в определенных территориях
Ukraine
Украины
suffer anyway, all territories to
страдают Все равно все территории в
varying degrees, always everywhere and everything And,
разной степени всегда везде и все И от
let’s say, military operations in Ukraine,
скажем так военных действий в Украине
in fact, the whole of Europe
страдает на самом деле вся Европа а вот
suffers, but you suffer, but including Yes, I
вы страдаете но в том числе Да я
suffered very much
пострадала очень сильно
Well, let’s just say I’m a farmer and I
Ну скажем так я фермер и занимаюсь
grow garlic
выращиванием чеснока
no, by no means is that the point,
нет ни в коем случае не в этом дело
but the problem is that I  I worked with a
а проблема в том что я работал с
Spanish family, they don’t deliver and in the spring
испанской семьей не поставляют и весной
this chemistry fell under sanctions now
это химия попала под санкции сейчас без
you can buy it without any problems, namely in the spring I
проблем можно купить а именно весной я
couldn’t buy That is, I ruined the harvest
не смог купить То есть я угробил урожай
for a large amount of money
на большое количество денег
this harvest. Well, why
потеряли вот этот урожай Ну я А почему
are you, because you had to
вы потому что надо было еще феврале
raise your ass back in February Where to buy
поднять свою задницу подумать Где купить
this chemistry
эту химию
[laugh] you
[смех]
shift responsibility to the
перекладываете до ответственность на
government
правительство
well, but for example, who is to blame for the fact
хорошо а вот например кто виноват в том
that they imposed sanctions against,
что вели санкции против
in my understanding, not Ukrainians, not Russians
в моем понимании не украинцы не русские
in this  not to blame
в этом не виноваты
And in fact, it wouldn’t matter if it was a
И на самом деле неважно была бы это
mess in Ukraine Yes, let’s say so, I
заварушка на Украине Да я так скажем так
’ll call it my own term Yes, not a layer, not a
назову это своим термином Да не слой не
war, I’m a mess, it
войну я заварушкой да
doesn’t matter if it started in Ukraine or
неважно началось бы это в Украине или
no sanctions would be introduced By the way,
нет санкции были бы введены Вот кстати у
you have someone from  grandfathers in the Second World War fought for the
вас кто-то из дедов во второй мировой за
proceeds Yes, both great-grandfathers, one
выручки воевал Да оба прадеда один
returned alone No,
вернулся один Нет
I don’t want
я не хочу
to reduce the
сводить
terminological dispute Why
терминологическим спором Почему Потому
Because many Ukrainians  you don’t understand the
что многие украинцы не понимает
specifics of the term, namely, a special
специфику термина именно специальная
military operation, why it’s not a war, but a
военная операция почему это не война а
bastard,
[__]
certain international ones,
определенные международные
as a rule, what is a war, what
как правило Что является войной Что
is the official one, you can say where
является официальной можно сказать где
to read these rules, read the conventions, the
эти правила почитать читайте конвенции
question is that today Russia is
вопрос в том что на сегодня Россия
limited in the contingent that it
ограничена в контингенте который она
can use on the territory of Ukraine
может использовать на территории Украины
if you still pay attention to this,
если вы все-таки уделите этому внимание
you will find documents I am a programmer with a
вы найдете документы я программист по
first degree in a second lawyer I was
первому образованию по второму юрист я
looking for there is no definition of a special
искал нету определения специальной
military operation there is a definition of a
военной операции есть определение именно
military operation related to the achievement of
военная операция связанная с достижением
specific let's do it if you say something
конкретных давайте так если вы что-то
I read this document
Я читал данный документ
I will not  I won’t give
я не буду давать я не буду
I won’t give a link Why
я не буду давать ссылку Почему Потому
Because I don’t want to spend time talking
что я не хочу тратить время разговора
that I want to spend on
который хочу потратить на получение
enjoying communication,
удовольствия от общения
it’s the search for a document to pass on to an
именно поиск документа чтобы передать
opponent the
оппоненту
opponent will find we have the
захочет оппонент найдет мы с вами имеем
same education I’m not a programmer
общее одно образование я не программист
don’t just look at  you are a lawyer by
не просто смотрите Вы юриста по своему
education Yes, I am a lawyer and
образованию Да я юриста и
time in the bar, look, it
время в адвокатуре смотрите вот
turns out that you just said that the
получается что вы просто сказали что
Ukrainians misunderstand the
украинцы неправильно
term correctly Why Russia
термин правильно понимает Почему Россия
uses this term
использует данный термин
It is the terminology that limits itself The
себя ограничивает именно терминология
use of terminology is a special
применение терминологии специальной
military operation Russia limits
военная операция Россия ограничивает
its military contingent on the territory
свой воинский контингент на территории
of Ukraine because  now they have
именно Украины Потому что сейчас провели
mobilized yes For understanding, Russia
мобилизацию да Для понимания России
legally considers the territories of Kherson,
юридически считает территории Херсонской
Donetsk, Luhansk and Zaporozhye
Донецкой Луганской и Запорожской
regions to be its territories, that is, to
областей своими территориями то есть для
protect its territory, Russia can
защиты своей территории Россия может
say
говорить
this is an occupation, but we understand that
это есть оккупация но мы понимаем что
let's just be reduced to estimates,
давайте проще будем сводиться оценочным
see this occupation This is an estimated self of
смотрите это оккупация Это оценочное я
Russian citizens, this is the annexation of the
российских граждан это присоединение
territory  don’t wait for people to
территории не подожди стоп того что люди
hold a referendum and a
провели референдум и
lawyer to a lawyer Don’t pay off a lawyer Yes,
юрист в юрист Не окупаться юрист Да вот
look from your point of view, then
смотрите с вашей точки зрения тогда
you can say that theft is also known
можно говорить что кража это тоже знаете
, for the one who steals it is not theft it is
вот для того кто ворует это не кража это
acquired  we are lawyers, and as
приобретение мы как юристы причем Я так
I understand it, you are expositions of Criminal
понимаю что вы экспозиции Уголовного
Law, too, a lawyer, yes, that is, closer to the
права тоже юрис да то есть ближе к
legal profession.
адвокатуре
This is not a problem because
Это не проблема потому что
Roman civil law is, after all,
Римская цивильное право это все-таки
Roman civil law.
Римская цивильное право это Базис того
right, I
я именно с позиции Уголовного права я
was a lawyer Well, look from the point of view of a
был адвокатом Ну смотри с точки зрения
thief of
вора
criminal law Unfortunately, the
уголовного законодательства К сожалению
criminal law of all our powers
Уголовное право всех наших держав она
does not protect us,
защищает не нас с вами
you just said that the occupation is
вы просто сказали что оккупация это
estimated because for Russia it is not an
оценочная потому что для России это не
occupation but an annexation, so I
оккупация а присоединение так я так
say that this is possible of course with  from the point of
говорю что так можно конечно с точки
view of criminals Let's then, based on
зрения преступников Давайте тогда исходя
the terminology of civil law
из терминологии цивильного права
End of
Закончились
prescription, look again, this was the same thing,
давность смотрите ещё раз это самое было
say that from the point of view of the aggressor Yes,
говорите что с точки зрения агрессора Да
this is not an occupation, this is the restoration of
это не оккупация это там восстановление
historical justice there, you understand
исторической справедливости понимаете
No, the motives are no longer interesting, this
Нет уже неинтересный мотивы это есть
is happening
получается
No, this annexation of the
Нет это присоединение
occupation can be considered Do not look it
оккупации можно считать Не смотрите
works  connection of territory  and outside
получается соединение территории вне
international law, you
международного законодательства вы
joined the low Federation in this
присоединились низкая Федерация в данной
situation
ситуации
used the conventions of international
использовала конвенции международного
law What if you were a lawyer
права Какие вот если ты как юрист
Look at
Посмотрите
you when you acted as a lawyer in court You
Вы когда в суде выступали как адвокат Вы
also spoke yourself
тоже говорили сами Посмотрите
Look you are definitely a lawyer, it turns out you are
Вы точно юрист получается смотрите Вы
now If you were practicing law
сейчас Если вы юридической практике были
and would you say  so and so yourself
и вы бы сказали так и так сами Найдите
Find which articles on which norm
на какие статьи на какую норму
the civil position is not, wait,
позицию гражданского нет подождите еще
look again If you are asserting something,
раз смотрите Вы если вы что-то
you are
утверждаете вы уже третий или четвертый
referring to some norms of law for the third or fourth time,
раз ссылаетесь на какие-то нормы права
I am in my free personal time,
нахожусь в свободное свое личное время
so look Wait, you refer to
так смотри Подождите вы ссылайтесь на
zero, you refer because you said
ноль вы ссылайтесь потому что вы сказали
that it was done According to international
что это сделано Согласно международных
standards, you referred And I say no
норм то вы сослались А я я говорю нет
stop According to what specific norms,
стоп Согласно каких конкретно норм
let's be like a lawyer I don't want a
давайте как юрист Я не хочу салат
salad  she herself decided what
народ Херсон она сама определился Что
the people of Kherson are with  look at Kherson they
такое народ Херсон смотрите Херсон
occupied the ethnic component of the
окупировали этническая составляющая
territory,
территория
let’s say when it was Here you came
давайте так когда был Вот вы пришли
occupied Kherson held some kind of
оккупировали Херсон провели там какой-то
pseudore there what right you are definitely an absolutely incompetent lawyer, of
псевдоре какое право Вы точно адвокат
course
абсолютно некомпетентный естественно
there is the right of the people
есть право народа
for example, there in
сдал то есть получается с например там в
Germany they didn’t capture part of the
Германии не захватывала там часть
Soviet Union there, they left Kherson, that is, it
Советского Союза ушли из Херсона То есть
turns out,
получается
I understand, that is, you are not a lawyer, you are
я понимаю То есть вы не адвокат вы
just a
просто
single bastard,
единичные [__]
subjective opinion
субъективное мнение
that you are a cynical bastard, no, wait, don’t
что вы циничный [__] нет подождите не
interrupt in the process, you understand
перебивайте в процессе Вы же понимаете
that you will receive a protest
что вы получите протест
I say it in person
Я говорю в лицо
you now when there is no protocol
вы сейчас когда протокол нет никакого
you did not follow it because you
вы не соблюдали его потому что вы
interrupted me now listen to me
перебивали меня теперь Слушайте меня
you come out here like this and u start
Вы выходите сюда так и э начинаете
justifying the occupation of an independent
оправдывать оккупацию независимого
state
государства начинаете закидывать псевдо
what is this convention look for
назвать что это есть конвенции ищите
d  you must look, I’m not doing it for you, it doesn’t
должны смотрите я вам не так это не
work If you work, you are the
работает Если вы работаете вы
norms of law Okay, I’ll say it officially Do you
нормы права Окей я скажу официально Вы
agree with the legal norms you gave to
согласны юридических норм вы дал
look
посмотреть
there is the legislation of the Russian
есть законодательстве Российской
Federation, it also says that it is written that
Федерации тоже написано что написано что
I would issue it, look for yourself Well, I’ll look for
выдал бы вот поищите сами Хорошо я поищу
this lawyer,
это юрист
it’s just a starball That is  how did he
это просто звездабол То есть как такое
bring only bribes shorter than a student
заносил только взятки короче студента
That’s all, this is a gasket between
Вот и все так это прокладка между
prosecutors dude just piles more than one
прокурорами чувак просто навалит не один
document he can’t say when they
документ не может он сказать когда его
say it like come on tell me you send
говорят типа давай ну скажи ты посылаешь
it to this document
на этот на этот документ
tell me I don’t know in short look for yourself you
скажи я не знаю короче сами ищите вы
look for such  game, then here you are an
сами ищете такую игру то вот ты
official dumbass,
официальный [__]
why is it written in the legislation of the
почему вот так законодательстве
Russian Federation that a dude
Российской Федерации написано чувака
immediately wakes up where
сразу просыпается где
you can’t find it yet So where does it say that
пока не найдешь Так где там написано что
you’re not Dolbaeva, you’re a dumbass here Sorry
ты не долбаева ты [__] вот Извините
for the swearing of such technical bastards, you just need to
за матюки таких технических ублюдка надо
just like that and let them go with him by the same
вот так просто и попускать их с ним же
method they are all  I begin to assert
методом они все начинают я утверждаю
something that this is all legal
что-то что это все законно
on the basis of what convention there is
на основании там конвенции каких
I won’t say, look for yourself on the
конвенций не скажу ищите сами на
basis of this, look for yourself, look for yourself Well, in
основании этого ищите сами ищите сами Ну
short, you look for everything yourself Glory to Ukraine
короче вот ты ищи сам все Слава Украине
Yes, she is tuned to everything Ukrainian
Да она настроен всему украинца
subscribe to the channel and comments
подписывайтесь на канал и комменты